brookdalecc.edu 2015-12-20

# Website Privacy Policy - Brookdale Community CollegeBrookdale Community College

## Brookdale Community College Web Privacy Guidelines

First and foremost, Brookdale Community College respects the privacy rights of our online visitors and we recognize the importance of information collected from you. We have developed these guidelines so that you can understand the choices you can make to preserve your privacy when browsing our site. Please read the following carefully. When you use our site, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

* * *

### Information Collection and Use

Our primary goal in collecting personal information, both identifying and non-identifying, is to make our site(s) and service(s) more relevant and rewarding for you to use.

Identifying information is collected when you choose to fill out a form to request additional information from us, or if you wish to have us contact you to resolve a problem or answer questions about the College. We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs, or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when we make changes to our services, to fulfill a request made by you, or to contact you. We will NOT provide your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes.

Non-identifying information is collected by our servers when you visit our website, and includes information about your domain, service provider, operating system, and browser, and also includes other non-identifying characteristics such as approximate age, regional location, search terms you may have used to find us, and any advertisements you clicked on to reach our site. We use this data, in aggregate, for research and reports on site activity, and to suggest and support changes we might make in our site to enhance viewers’ experiences. We do not associate your IP address with any other identifiable information to identify you personally, except when necessary to comply with legally binding requests from Law Enforcement.

* * *

### Cookies

To enhance and personalize your experience, some of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files that your web browser places on your computer’s hard drive to store your preferences. We use cookies and other technologies to passively collect demographic data, personalize your experience on the site, and monitor advertisements and other activities. When using cookies, we do not store personally identifiable information within the cookie. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. To find out about how to opt out of this type of data collection, please go to <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

* * *

### Collection Of Information By Third-Party Sites

Some of our site(s) and service(s) contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

* * *

### Law Enforcement

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose and information about you to government or law enforcement officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of the College or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

* * *

### Privacy Of Children Younger Than 13 Years

Brookdale Community College is concerned about the privacy of young children and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13 years of age. We suggest that you become involved with your child’s access to the Internet and to our site to ensure that his or her privacy is well protected.

* * *

### If you have any questions about this privacy policy

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the content or practices of our website, please contact:

Brookdale Community College  
Laurie K. Bender  
Director, Marketing, Website & Creative Services  
765 Newman Springs Road  
Lincroft, NJ 07738  
732-224-2059  

* * *
